theanonymouswriter.com 2018-05-03

# Privacy Policy - The Anonymous Writer

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at [www.theanonymouswriter.com/contact-us](mailto:contact@theanonymouswriter.com).

At www.theanonymouswriter.com we consider the privacy of our visitors to be extremely important. This privacy policy document describes in detail the types of personal information is collected and recorded by www.theanonymouswriter.com and how we use it.

Upon visiting theanonymouswriter.com, you agree to the following terms and conditions. If you do not wish to be bound by these terms and conditions, you should not visit the website.

  * You hereby agree that theanonymouswriter.com has the sole right to modify or remove the contents of the website without any prior notice. In addition, you agree that theanonymouswriter.com holds the right to publish contents from its subsidiaries, affiliates, and third-parties.
  * The trademark, logo, and content appearing on the theanonymouswriter.com are protected by intellectual property laws and international intellectual property treaties. You are authorised to make offline copy of the content for non-commercial use only.
  * When you submit content to theanonymouswriter.com, you declare that the content if plagiarism free. The Anonymous Writer reserves the royalty-free right to publish, modify, and distribute the submitted content on the web and social media.
  * The Anonymous Writer website may include hyperlinks containing third-party content or advertisements. You agree that theanonymouswriter.com, in no way, is responsible for products or content available on those websites.
  * You agree that theanonymouswriter.com, in no event; will be liable for any loss, direct or otherwise, occurring from the use of this website.
  * You understand and concur with the above terms and conditions as a general agreement between you and theanonymouswriter.com.  
Additional terms and conditions may be subjected to the use of third-party content.
  * theanonymouswriter.com reserves all the right to amend/modify the terms and conditions at sole discretion without prior notice.

 **Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.theanonymouswriter.com makes use of log files. These files merely logs visitors to the site – usually a standard procedure for hosting companies and a part of hosting services’s analytics. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. This information is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

 **Cookies and Web Beacons  
**www.theanonymouswriter.com uses cookies to store information about visitors’ preferences, to record user-specific information on which pages the site visitor accesses or visits, and to personalize or customize our web page content based upon visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.  

******Third Party Privacy Policies  
**You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.theanonymouswriter.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites. [What Are Cookies?](http://www.privacypolicyonline.com/what-are-cookies)

 **Children’s Information**  
We believe it is important to provide added protection for children online. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children to observe, participate in and/or monitor and guide their online activity.  
www.theanonymouswriter.com does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian believes that www.theanonymouswriter.com has in its database the personally-identifiable information of a child under the age of 13, please contact us immediately (using the contact in the first paragraph) and we will use our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.

 **Online Privacy Policy Only  
**This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website and regarding information shared and/or collected there.  
This policy does not apply to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.

 **Consent  
**By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms.

 **Update  
**This Privacy Policy was last updated on: Monday, July 13th, 2015.

 _Should we update, amend or make any changes to our privacy policy, those changes will be posted here._
